salenearn.com 2016-04-04

# Privacy Policy - SaleNearn

Our privacy policy describes how we collect, use and share personal information to help the SaleNearn and to keep it safe. This privacy policy may be updated by us at anytime without any prior notice .In this privacy statement personal information includes details or information of an individual including the personal details like contact and other personal information.

**COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Our site registration form reqests users to enter their personal information such as name,email,contact number.we use this information to send the user requests regarding the services, promotional offers of site.contact information may be used to contact customers only when necessary.SaleNearn use third-party advertising companies like google to serve ads when you visit our website. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
All information treated as strictly confidential and we does not and will not disclose or share such confidential information to / with any external organization. We will not rent or sell users personal information to third parties. 

In some cases we may be required to disclose user's personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority and in case of any fraud in transactions saleNearn reserves right to make use of the personal information in investigation or judicial process. Other scenario in which we may disclose personal information is to respond to claims made by the user which violates the rights or safety of the information. We also disclose the personal information with: - Agencies who help detect or prevent potentially illegal acts and with the service providers who help our business operations 

**IP ADDRESSES**  
SaleNearn may use the users IP address to identify users IP and gather broad demographic information, diagnose problems with our server and administer the Site. We provide logout option to ensure your safety when you are using a public or shared system. 

Editing your information: User can modify his/her personal details any time or they can contact our customer service info[at]salenearn.com To review the information.we delete your personal information when we no longer need it or on users consent. 

**SECURITY OF DATA**  
We take proper measures to ensure security of the users personal information and we protect it against any kind of misuse or alteration of information by keeping in mind the sensitivity of the information. However,no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure by unknown parties,to overcome this we use a secure data transmission by using network servers in a secure encrypted mode specially when accessing credit card transactions.we cannot ensure or warrant the security of information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.But still we take steps to protect the information from misuse or loss or from unauthorized access. 

**UNSUBSCRIBE:**  
When user no longer wishes to receive any alerts or promotional information from the site he/she ay choose unsubscribe option.once user opts unsubscribe they will not be receiving communications from us, their information will be removed from our database. 

**CONTACTUS**  
You can contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy polices in connection with this Site. Our collection, disclosure or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact us at [info@SaleNearn.com](mailto:info@SaleNearn.com)
